I would like to thank Bhai Ji and Piyush Sir
and the next presentation will be a
great presentation by Dr. Judge Sheikh. He is from
Prayagraj. Two Saeed Bhai
is a dentist and his analysis is great.
He gave a presentation on ICICI Lombard
last time and we got a lot of
positive reviews about it.
So today's presentation is there and as
Bhai has written about multibag and potential,
I would like to know from Jain Bhai whether we should buy this stock right now.
So for this excellent
presentation, I would like to invite
Dr. Jayshree from Prayagraj. Welcome.
We should look at insurance.
Insurance itself is an instrument
which transfers risk. Mainly
our financial risk, whether it is related to
our health or our assets or to our
life, we
transfer that risk to some other company.
We transfer it to that insurance company.
Right,
sector and overall sector, whether it has growth in India, it is
important to know this first.
Before knowing this company, if we
talk about its booster,
why will it grow, insurance sector 4 of all
insurance sectors  Firstly, our
awareness is increasing. Earlier, we rarely heard
about life insurance and health insurance.
Nowadays,
it is being talked about in every village because what about us now.
Connectivity is increasing.
People have started knowing that insurance is something
which benefits us. So,
our awareness is increasing.
What is our income now? If we
talk about capital income, then right now it is spent on
food and living.
As our per capita income will increase, we will
see that in the future, when the per
capita income increases, we will
also invest in our security, that is, we will
buy insurance.
Last but not the least, the most important
factor for the boost of this entire sector is
market penetration and
market density. If we talk about India, then at present
our per capita spends approximately Rs 6500 for
its insurance.
If we talk about developed countries here, then
how much do they spend approximately? If we
talk about that, then in terms of Indian Rupees,
a person spends approximately ₹6 lakh.  The
average spend is why their income
is higher, but we will see in the coming time that
this under penetration, under density will
give growth to the entire sector. Now
this is in the initial phase of the insurance sector,
we will see it growing like it has happened
in other countries. Right friends, if we
look at it this way,
we can divide the insurance industry into two big parts -
life and non-life insurance.
Life insurance includes your tomb close
etc. Like which big company is life insurance?
LIC.
Apart from this, whatever insurance is there other than life insurance
and comes under non-life insurance
or general insurance,
if we do main partition in this also, then mainly there are four
types of companies,
our public sector companies
come at number two, our private
sector companies come at number two, some companies
which provide only health insurance are
standard on health assured and there are
specialized assured which
provide insurance for some conditions
and if we talk about general insurance non-life
insurance companies, then there are
approximately 35 companies in India which are working
in this sector.
If we look at the market of these 35 companies  If we look at the shares,
who has the largest market share in general insurance,
friends, New India Insurance
Company is the largest
market share, after that comes ICICI
Lombard, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance is a
government insurance company,
what happens to them,
where there is a need and where there are more chances of getting clamps, so in a
government company, we get that much profit, whereas the private
sector companies take
care that
their profits remain intact, that is why they
provide less insurance in those sectors where there are
more chances of getting clamps, right,
only private sector companies, if we
talk about the top three companies, then which are
ICC,
Bajaj, Alis and HDFC Ego, so these are the three
big companies, the top three companies of general insurance,
ICICI, Bajaj, Alis Gypsy,
if we want to invest in them, then
how can we invest in them,
ICC is directly listed,
so what should we do, so what should
we do,
what is the growth of these general insurance companies, if we
look at the growth of general insurance, then last  If
we look at the income in the last 14 years, the entire sector has grown by 15%
and since the last year, if we
look at GDP alone, it has grown by 11%.
This is an emerging industry and we will grow by
20% in the coming time. So, which
lipstick companies do we have?
Which ones does ICICI
have? Right friends, it has a mark of 42%. If we
look at the sales, the biggest
gross premium collected
in the entire sector is
Prabal National Insurance with 42%.
Both of these are government sector companies,
which have a
market share of 56%. But
for ICICI, which was earning the third position in gross premium,
how much does it earn in profit?
Right flex at the second position with a profit share of about 36%. And if we
look at the margin against the cross premium, then as we
already told that the margins of the comment sector are
not that good, so
ICICI has a good margin here
compared to other companies. Right friends.
Friends, the first thing we
should know is that in the last financial
report we presented,
ICC is always considered to be the
best company in its sector in terms of property in which
we can invest.
So before investing in ICC, let
us know about ICC. ICC
started in 2001 as a joint venture with ICC Bank Financial Holdings Limited, Toronto. Today, it has become India's
largest private general insurance
company. If we look at
its results, if we
talk about the results for the half year, friends, then in the
half year result, it showed a growth of 25% in net premium. The
growth in total income was 11%. The
growth in expenses was 7%
and profit is 47%. The
special thing to note is that net premium
income saw a growth of 25%, but why did the total income
grow by only 11%?
Because they have another income
apart from net premium, that is income from
investment. We did not see any growth there.  The
total income is
not as expected. If we
talk about its segmental revenue, from
where is its segmented revenue coming from, its
biggest source of income was
motor insurance. The
total growth was of motor insurance. Motor insurance has a
share of 49% in it and the growth in it
in the last quarter was 4% and
as friends, we had said that
investment income which is of 13%, there was a
growth of -8% in it, hence we did
not get it as per our expectation here. If we talk about its expenses,
friends,
what is the biggest expense of any insurance company,
we saw here a total growth of 10% in it.
Another special thing to note is that in the
claims outstanding, that is, the
claims which are ahead but have not been settled yet,
we saw an increase of 11% in it. We
saw this in the last result also.
What will be its effect? ​​Its effect will be that
in the coming time, we will
not get to see that much in claims pay.
You are with you.  In the earnings call they gave this year, the
management told them that there are
two major
recoveries. The recovery is happening in the economy in
all sectors. So
why is the recovery happening in the economy? Our
demand is increasing.
Consumption is good, okay, and
credit as well. But some things that
can stop the economy's growth,
whether it is global inflation, strong rollers, and this
zero quality tension that remains. So
overall, if the economy grows,
we will also see good growth in the insurance sector.
We saw that good growth was seen in the sale of digital vehicles. So,
what will happen if
cars, bikes, motors are sold, then their
insurance was
seen,
along with health insurance, they also
saw good growth. Along with this, the
GDP growth they saw in H2 this year was
15%.
Overall demand was good. They
told this in their call and what we
also saw in its results. Right friends,
what does its trend say?  It is important to know
about the historical friend. Talking about the
net premium, from 2006 to 2022,
it has collected 18 times the net premium in the last 16 years at a CAGR of 15%.
If we
also look at the expenses, then the last step which was
collected in blind of about 13.5 thousand crores, it has
collected more than that in its childhood.
If you look at its profit, then
from 2006 till now till 2022, it has increased
its profit by 25 times in 16 years.
Friends, if we look at the profit of H1,
as we saw last year, the
profit was less, but this year it has made more than half of its lifetime
high profit of about
14,500 crores, i.e., approximately
940 crores. In H1,
we should again expect lifetime high profit here.
Talking about research, it has increased
its result 67 times in the last 16 years
and last year it increased it
From a result of Rs 8600 crore, it increased its
result to approximately Rs 93100 crore in H1.
Friends, if we talk about its current and see
what is the trend of this quarter, then we see that
in 9 months it had a growth of 20%,
sales net premium income
29% net premium growth came in X1, we
saw 25%, so we can expect
that by the end of this year it will grow at least 23%
in net frame, very fast.
If we look at the profit, in 9 months - there was a
group of 50%,
mines were found in the unit,
we expected that
we would get a very good profit but it did
not come as per our expectation, the same was because
their income from investment did
not come as per our expectation, so
we saw a growth of 42% in H1,
right friends, we can expect
that by hearing we should see a growth of 40%
in profit, so what is our short
term growth  What should be the net premium of 23%
and the short term profit, the
expectation is 40% and
in the long term, we can expect a close premium of 13% and a
profit of 13% from the company,
so the company which collected a lifetime high net premium of
approximately 13 1/2 thousand crores,
we can expect that this year it should
collect a net premium of at least Rs. 13000 crores and
by 2035 this company will be collecting a net premium of approximately Rs. 72000 crores,
friends,
if we talk about its profit,
when did the lifetime profit come,
in 2021 it was approximately Rs. 14.5 lakhs, by the
end of this year we will again
see a lifetime profit of approximately Rs. 1770 crores
and in 2035 this company will
make a profit of around Rs. 700 crores, then the
value comes out, then
our expected value is 230, approximately Rs. 1360
and this same value will be our expectation till 2035, Rs.
5000  It is
also important to know from the chart whether it is
available at fair value friends as
we know that the entire insurance
sector is
insurance, first say life insurance, so
here we are getting this stock below its share value,
mains it is not getting very expensive
but
technically we are getting
a good
time range between 31000 to 1300,
our short term target will be around
1798 mains around 18, you should
keep it with you because general
insurance is that
time when the entire sector
is under pressure, that pressure gives us time for accumulation, do
research or talk to your advisor,
thank you, thank you friends
brother, great presentation, you told that there is
tremendous growth in ICICI Insurance
and the demand is also good, which was very
good to hear because many sectors have been
hit suddenly, so friends ICICI
General Insurance is a stock of multiply
and as we see that there is
growth in any country, then the beginning is always
roti kapda makaan, every family, if we look at any
country  Initially, in the past several years,
our previous generation's entire
struggle was on food, clothing, shelter, education,
but now the situation is good, everyone's income is
increasing well, so everyone has
insurance or security for retirement
because after basic needs, there should be
security, as we have
seen in comedy, many people's hospital
bills increased so much that they suffered a lot of
financial loss, similarly we will see
that whatever different products we buy
in our house, whether it is a TV or a refrigerator,
nowadays for protection we do this, we
take insurance for them or make
provision for their maintenance, so whatever is
important for us, as Bhai told that a lot of
term around has been done in the vehicle sector
and in the vehicle sector also
you are getting to do after booking, so
insurance of vehicles and bikes will be sold, so many such
things are supporting it well,
so I would like to thank Jahir Bhai for giving such a wonderful presentation
and friends, I would like to tell you that the
best leading
insurance company in the world has become very close to
Multiforce 200
Our company has grown 400 times. This company has just started running, so
many investors ask
where to invest in the stock. Tell me which small
stock is going to bring very good prospects.
So friends, this is the van of D
stock and for such a great stock, I would
like to request Piyush Sir to
give his complete opinion on the ICICI presentation. Welcome Sir, the
PPT you have made is absolutely amazing,
absolutely set brother, the rest will not be removed, it is simple and
effective, right, let me
tell everyone about it in advance because the last time
you made such a presentation in the ICC World,
some people commented that it was just an
investor presentation of ICICI Lombard.
I would like to tell you that this is like this
in every company,
he has made it himself, but he has
made it so beautiful by using colors like people, that
you might feel that his own
recharge for his hard work
came first on profit, the
profitability is good, it is absolutely good.
Generally, insurance is a growing sector in
India.
Friends, if the
name of retail comes up, then the name of
insurance and investment also comes up along with it.
Definitely friends, insurance sector
company should be in the portfolio. Now if
you had
kept an insurance company in the portfolio, if you take our point in mind, then for the last
2 years you have not earned anything in insurance, not even equal,
because for the last 2 years all the
insurance companies are on correction mode, now there is
no need to know why this is,
because due to Covid, there were a lot of claims, but now the
profitability will keep increasing, friends, we should be
hopeful that we will get good profitability,
friends,
strong gross
brother told me, I think till 23, there is a
group of ICICI people, so
friends, what do you think, is the
growth good, is it okay or is it complete,
friends, there is explosive demand, Tata Consumer
growth till 11 is still good, so there is
TV demand all day long, so it is telling you that
people are paying the premium of every house, it is important to pay attention that there is
no profit here, there is no profit because
friends, if a combined ratio is seen, then it is
not good, right,
I repeat, more than 100 means that
till five, more
money has been spent than the net premium, so 105  Note: Good, but pay
attention to last year
because the ratios are
not good. We already know that
high claims and bribes are not good. Now, if the
claims have decreased, then investment income has
decreased. There is no need to worry.
Friends, this is a product of multi-year rally,
even retired people can definitely invest if they want
because the dividend will be consistent.
Right now, the very good thing is that
it is not broken, it is very broken, more
than 2 years old, but read the hit. Friends, at such times,
people who collect stocks do
not have to chase the lion.
Don't do it. Next, see if the combined
ratio comes below 100. Yes, as the
combined ratio goes down, your shares will
break, then you will buy it. Is it equivalent to collecting from now? So,
all is well,
but there is one advantage Mansoori, just let me check it, is it very good?
Jai Faizan Mansoori for you,
once again, tell me the value data
in it. How much do you expect from your sales and profit?
Okay
[Music]
Tell me 2013,
that too.  It should be 6 times
or thank you very good
access will have to be given
presentation and friends this is ICCI
number, multiply it as sir also
told and we are also seeing in the chart right now that
it is at a good level, friends
such shares which are available cheap right now are
important because look like you,
it had made a top of 1700 and is almost
near ₹1000 now, so if you
took the risk and bought it at a good level, then you
get good results immediately,
many people see after the breakout,
but if as you did not tell,
if you buy at good levels, then from the breakout